



Contact

551-998-7611

homesbygabby@gmail.com

in www.linkedin.com/in/gabrielaespinal

www.homesbygabbie.com

Skills

Sales	
Marketing	
Real Estate	
Yardi	
Entrata	
MS Word	
MS Excel	

Certifications

Indeed

Computer Skills: PC Expert

Real Estate Profici

Customer Focus & Orientation

Highly Proficient

LinkedIn

Microsoft Excel Microsoft Word Microsoft Outlook Proficient

About me



Assistant Property Management with 5+ years of experience seeking new opportunities where my customer service background and education can be utilized to the fullest, providing customers with the highest quality of service and investors with a high rate of return on their investment. Hospitality Management Associate. Real Estate License in process. Personable, organized and task-oriented.

Experience



Lincoln Property Company

O Aug 2020-Present

Assistant Property Manager Atlanta, GA, United States

- *Responsible for implementing lease renewal and resident retention programs.
- *Manage resident relations issues, which includes taking resident phone calls, requests and concerns.
- *Analyze weekly leasing reports and forecast occupancy trends.
- *Assist with developing and tracking marketing strategies, including advertising, promotions and publications.
- *Manage rent collections, late notices and posting rent.
- *Review and inspect vacancies, make-ready apartments and models.
- *Inspect the property for community policy violations, needed repairs and overall landscaping.

1170 Apartment Corp

O Jan 2016 - Aug 2020

Assistant Property Manager

New Jersey, United States

- *Help manage 26 Buildings for a total of 1170 units in a 35 acres land
- *Advertise units and negotiate lease terms
- *Perform tenant screenings
- *Responsible for implementing lease renewal
- *Collect rent on a monthly basis and handle late payments in a timely manner
- *Maintain property by addressing tenant complaints, completing repairs, occupancy
- *Create, mentor and manage a cohesive property maintenance team

Smart Realty

O Jan 2019-Present

Property Sales Consultant / Leasing Specialist

New Jersey, United States

- *Generating leads and turning them into opportunities for sales and rentals
- *Contacting potential customers via telephone & email
- *Arranging meetings with prospects in order to tour property
- *Front office customer service
- *Preparing lease documentation, property inspections, completing move-in and out paperwork and procedures

Education



Real Estate

O Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Kovats Real Estate School

Associate's Degree

O Dec 2010-Jan 2014

Hospitality Administration / Management Bergen Community College